<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jamie.so</title>
    <link>https://jamie.so/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jamie.so</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 11:45:40 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamie.so/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>sed</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/sed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 11:45:40 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/sed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;sed&lt;/code&gt;, search and replace text using regex.  You have text and you want to change it&amp;hellip; you need sed.  Works well over multiple files when combined with &lt;code&gt;find&lt;/code&gt;. Pre installed on most operating systems just waiting for you to use it.  However using the BSD version of sed that comes with OS X can cause you pain&amp;hellip; so sometimes for compatibility &lt;code&gt;awk&lt;/code&gt; is your friend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chamber</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/chamber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 23:39:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/chamber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Secrets management &amp;hellip; the bane of automation in enterprises!  If you are lucky enough to use aws parameter store and kms (every SecArch loves kms, so that part should be straight forward).  Then you can manage your secrets using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/segmentio/chamber&#34;&gt;chamber&lt;/a&gt;.  A tool that allows you to read a secret from parameter store and place them in your environment.  It pairs fantastically well with aws-vault for identity management.  Excellent to use as glue between an encrypted secret in parameter store and terraform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aws-vault</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/aws-vault/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 21:52:42 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/aws-vault/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Need to use the awscli and don&amp;rsquo;t have time to implement federation?  Can&amp;rsquo;t connect to existing identity systems due to the skunkworks nature of your project? Have many seperate clients and aws accounts to deal with? &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/99designs/aws-vault&#34;&gt;aws-vault&lt;/a&gt; is here to save you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>awscli and jq</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/aws-jq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 23:10:17 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/aws-jq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah the classic partnerships, hot chocolate and marshmallows , hot dogs and sauce, hot aws cli and jq. Some days the GUI just won&amp;rsquo;t easily tell you what you want to know.  The AWS CLI and jq to the rescue!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>github code signing</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/gpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 22:53:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/gpg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Signing your code is an important part of verifying your identity to an SCM platform.  Particularly with a system like Github Enterprise where spoofing your colleagues email address can make your commits appear to come from them.  Enforcing signing on the repository would enable you to determine if this has taken place and allow you to verify this important part of the software supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>.plan</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/plan/</guid>
      <description> reading:  Blondie24: Playing at the Edge of AI  watching:  The Thin Blue Line (again)  playing:  Automachef Slay the Spire  thinking:  How can the concept of an immutable team deal with the reality of constant change? How can I better spend my time with my family?  studying:  Certified Kubernetes Administrator  working:  Deakin Genie  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about me</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/about/</guid>
      <description>It has probably been ten seconds since I last thought about computers in some way.
I am facinated by the connections between technical systems, including the developers, stakeholders and users of those systems.
Sitting in a darkened room looking at a screen is pure fun and when the kids are safely in bed I like nothing more than coding, gaming or simply learning but it is always made better when someone brings me a cup of tea and excitedly asks what I am working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact me</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>email: jbgmoore@gmail.com
twitter: https://twitter.com/jbgmoore
li: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jbgmoore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>resume</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>Career Goal Contribute to an organisation by working with engineers to design and develop their continuous delivery systems and cloud engineering patterns.
Skills and Experience  I have worked as a Software/Systems/DevOps Engineer for over twenty years. In that time, I have designed, built and maintained a wide variety of computer systems. I am certified and proficient in designing and implementing solutions on AWS as proven over the last five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>talks</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/talks/</guid>
      <description>This page is intentionally blank to encourage me to fill it in :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>