<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jamie.so</title>
    <link>https://jamie.so/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jamie.so</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 23:10:17 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamie.so/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS and JQ</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/aws-jq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 23:10:17 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/aws-jq/</guid>
      <description>Ah the classic partnerships, hot chocolate and marshmallows , hot dogs and sauce, hot aws cli and jq.
Installation The aws cli can be installed like so:
pip install awscli And jq, thus:
brew install jq Top Tips Before you go crazy with jq alone&amp;hellip; remember your friend --filters on the aws cli &amp;hellip; because there is nothing like hitting the api limits by running a query over all your instances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>github code signing</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/gpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 22:53:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/gpg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Signing your code is an important part of verifying your identity to an SCM platform.  Particularly with a system like Github Enterprise where spoofing your colleagues email address can make your commits appear to come from them.  Enforcing signing on the repository would enable you to determine if this has taken place and allow you to verify this import part of the software supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>.plan</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/plan/</guid>
      <description> reading:  Blondie24: Playing at the Edge of AI  watching:  The Thin Blue Line (again)  playing:  Automachef Slay the Spire  thinking:  How can the concept of an immutable team deal with the reality of constant change? How can I better spend my time with my family?  studying:  Certified Kubernetes Administrator  working:  Deakin Genie  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about me</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/about/</guid>
      <description>It has probably been ten seconds since I last thought about computers in some way.
I am facinated by the connections between technical systems, including the developers, stakeholders and users of those systems.
Sitting in a darkened room looking at a screen is pure fun and when the kids are safely in bed I like nothing more than coding, gaming or simply learning but it is always made better when someone brings me a cup of tea and excitedly asks what I am working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact me</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>email: jbgmoore@gmail.com
twitter: https://twitter.com/jbgmoore
linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jbgmoore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>resume</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/resume/</guid>
      <description>Career Goal Contribute to an organisation by working with engineers to design and develop their continuous delivery systems and cloud engineering patterns.
Skills and Experience  I have worked as a Software/Systems/DevOps Engineer for over twenty years. In that time, I have designed, built and maintained a wide variety of computer systems. I am certified and proficient in designing and implementing solutions on AWS as proven over the last five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>talks</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/page/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/page/talks/</guid>
      <description>This page is intentionally blank to encourage me to fill it in :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>