<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on jamie.so</title>
    <link>https://jamie.so/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on jamie.so</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 23:39:46 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamie.so/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chamber</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/chamber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 23:39:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/chamber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Secrets management &amp;hellip; the bane of automation in enterprises!  If you are lucky enough to use aws parameter store and kms (every SecArch loves kms, so that part should be straight forward).  Then you can manage your secrets using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/segmentio/chamber&#34;&gt;chamber&lt;/a&gt;.  A tool that allows you to read a secret from parameter store and place them in your environment.  It pairs fantastically well with aws-vault for identity management.  Excellent to use as glue between an encrypted secret in parameter store and terraform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aws-vault</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/aws-vault/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 21:52:42 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/aws-vault/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Need to use the awscli and don&amp;rsquo;t have time to implement federation?  Can&amp;rsquo;t connect to existing identity systems due to the skunkworks nature of your project? Have many seperate clients and aws accounts to deal with? &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/99designs/aws-vault&#34;&gt;aws-vault&lt;/a&gt; is here to save you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>awscli and jq</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/aws-jq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 23:10:17 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/aws-jq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah the classic partnerships, hot chocolate and marshmallows , hot dogs and sauce, hot aws cli and jq. Some days the GUI just won&amp;rsquo;t easily tell you what you want to know.  The AWS CLI and jq to the rescue!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>github code signing</title>
      <link>https://jamie.so/post/gpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 22:53:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>jbgmoore@gmail.com (jamie moore)</author>
      <guid>https://jamie.so/post/gpg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Signing your code is an important part of verifying your identity to an SCM platform.  Particularly with a system like Github Enterprise where spoofing your colleagues email address can make your commits appear to come from them.  Enforcing signing on the repository would enable you to determine if this has taken place and allow you to verify this important part of the software supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>